[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
MkvDrama.net
A wave of simultaneous kidnappings has struck seven cities in Asia!
The incidents happened in Tokyo,
Seoul, Singapore, Bangkok,
Manila, Taipei, and Naha.
Seven cities in total.
Red rose petals were found at the scene of each crime.
Breaking news! Abductions in seven Asian cities!
KIDNAP GAME
36 HOURS UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
TOKYO
AM 07:02 JST
DETECTIVE TOSHIRO NIIDE
Saori!
You're crushing me.
Oh...
Thanks for waking me.
-What's that? -I bought it for tomorrow.
Tomorrow? The Tokyo Festival?
No.
Did you forget?
No way I'd forget. It's our... tenth.
Our gold anniversary. Wait, silver?
Uh-huh. Your coffee's getting cold.
Thanks for protecting me.
It's bigger than ever this year.
The festivities include a parade and a greeting from foreign guests.
A large turnout is expected.
Traffic restrictions will be placed around the venue.
The police will dispatch units to direct traffic and enhance security.
I wonder if we'll see the fireworks.
The new, big condo might block the view.
No. I mean can we see them together?
Sure we can.
Aren't you on duty?
I am.
But I get off after the parade at five.
It starts at seven, so you'll make it.
Yeah. Delicious, thanks.
What about you?
I think I can get off early, so I'll cook us a nice dinner.
A nice dinner, huh? Then could you grab some champagne?
Don't you mean beer? Hey, I found a delicious craft beer.
Looking forward to it.
That was delicious.
-Well, I'll be off. -Have a good day.
Grandma? Michiyo?
Mr. Tadokoro, is your wife missing?
Yeah, she's probably lost again.
Did anything unusual happen?
Ah... the bread for breakfast.
Bread?
She said something about forgetting to buy it.
Mrs. Tadokoro! Good morning. It's me, Niide.
Your husband's looking for you. Let's go home.
Okay? Let's go.
That's one thousand yen.
Huh? Ah...
You don't have your wallet... I guess not.
Mind the steps.
Okay, let's go.
-You got bread. -This bakery is delicious!
Is that so?
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
SEOUL
AM 08:08 KST
DOCTOR HAN KIJU
HANDS OF GOD DOCTOR ENJOYS EASY RETIREMENT
WIFE IS COSMETICS MOGUL BLIND DAUGHTER IS VIOLIN PRODIGY
ALL BECAUSE OF HIS DAUGHTER'S FAILED SURGERY?!
Rian?
Let's get ready for school.
I'll take that.
Rian.
It was great. Thanks.
Sure.
Up you go.
Have you read this?
Such a load of garbage.
Don't let it bother you.
They're even sensationalizing Rian.
Rian, about your recital tomorrow... Mom might not make it.
It can't be helped if Mom is busy. What about you, Dad?
Me? I'll go for sure.
You won't have an urgent surgery?
Don't worry.
There are plenty of other good doctors.
I see. But don't mind me if they need you, okay?
Your job is to save people's lives, after all.
Yes, that's right.
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
SINGAPORE
FLIGHT ATTENDANT JANICE LAU
Sorry, I'm late. Got stuck in traffic.
Janice!
Sorry.
He proposed?!
Not yet.
But he did booked Monti Marina Bay tomorrow.
No way! You’ve almost got your meal ticket!
What are you talking about? The meal ticket’s just a bonus.
Tony’s a really sweet guy.
What do you think I should wear tomorrow?
You know, I don’t want to overdo it, y’know...
It’s not about clothes. It’s about showing up on time.
Don’t worry, I’ll be on time even if it kills me.
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
BANGKOK
AM 08:46 ICT
Aum.
HOSTESS AUM THANAWAN
You're still smoking this?
I thought you already quit!
I don't use it anymore.
Then what's this?
Are you still dealing? Why, Aum?!
It's the only way I know how to live!
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
MANILA
PM 02:07 PHT
TAXI DRIVER MIGUEL GARCIA
Are you from Japan?
Yeah, we're on our honeymoon.
-Hey, your Japanese is great! -Thanks.
I used to work in Tokyo.
Have you been to the Manila Baywalk Dolomite beach?
They say if you see that emerald sea at...
3 p.m, if you see the sea, your love will last forever.
It doesn’t say that in the guidebook.
It’s veery famous among the youth in Manila.
My 20-year-old granddaughter told me.
-Wow! -Wow!
-It's so beautiful. -It really is.
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
TAIPEI
AM 10:48 TST
HOUSEWIFE CHRISTINA LIN
What's wrong?
You're not filming again are you?
No! And I deleted the old video.
Don't you believe me?
Christina...
You're my one true love.
I want to be with you.
Don't you trust me?
I do.
ATRA FLOWER SHOP
NAHA
PM 12:49 JST
SYSTEMS ENGINEER KURANOSUKE HIGA
It's ready. I made your favorite.
I told you that we'll eat out.
What for?
Would it be okay if I invite some old friends over?
Like former co-workers and neighbors.
You think they'll like that? They'll only resent you.
I miss them.
You're here now! In my world!
Don't you get it? Your son is a world-famous CEO!
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
30 HOURS UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
This is the police.
Shut up.
I'm Niide. Community Safety Division, Shinjuku Central.
We got a call about a child screaming.
Get lost.
Hey...
What a jerk. That's a wife-beater for sure.
-Stop it! -You shut your mouth!
-Stop it! -Shut up! Get away from me!
My life's a mess because of you!
Stop it, Dad!
Get off, you little shit!
-You piece of shit! -You okay?
Stop it!
What's the matter?
We can't just leave.
Next, we make an incision in the dura along the nerve
to expose C3 and give us a wider surgical field.
This allows us to temporarily clamp the blood vessel,
making it safer to perform aneurysm clipping and tumor resection.
Dr. Han, thank you for the lecture.
Please.
Have you thought about it? I'd like you to take on that surgery.
Like I said before, I have another lecture scheduled.
The patient's a big-shot politician with pull in the art world.
Think of your daughter.
I'm sorry.
Now if you'll excuse me.
Will she lose her sight?
You said it would succeed.
You said you'd fix her eyes.
Excuse me, Dr. Han?
I'm Park Dongkuk, Midum Funeral Services.
Good luck to your daughter for her recital.
Don't look baffled.
I know everything about you, Doctor.
So if you ever need help, let me know.
That probably won't be necessary.
We can't do anything without a warrant.
Police! Open up!
Open up!
I told you to get lost.
Niide!
Hey!
Hyodo! Hold him down!
Get your filthy hands off!
Put your anger aside. Show your kindness...
Kindness that shields the weak...
That's the right thing to do.
-Hyodo. -Yes.
Come on out. You okay? C'mon.
It's okay now.
You protected your mom.
You did well.
You're not pregnant.
I see.
My mistake.
Might be good to get your husband tested.
Okay.
SAORI NEW MESSAGE
24 HOURS UNTIL THE GAME STARTS
"Twenty-four hours until the game starts."
-Niide! -Coming.
My sincerest apologies.
For what?
For this...
How many times do I have to tell you?
I didn't hit him.
Damn right you didn't! You think we're in the seventies?!
But sir, you also...
-Huh? -Er, nothing.
Well, now you're outta my hair.
Transferal?
ASSIGNED TO HOMICIDE DIVISION
NISHI-SHINJUKU MEDICAL CENTER
-Take care. -You too.
Might be good to get your husband tested.
-Yes? -Sorry, I'll be late tonight.
Are you going somewhere? There's something I'd like to talk about.
I got transferred to the Homicide Division.
The Homicide Division? That's great!
-Niide, let's go! -Okay.
Saori! We're borrowing Niide!
They want to celebrate.
Can't do without the guest of honor.
Sorry. Bye.
Congratulations.
Tonight, we're here to celebrate...
Cheers!
You just had to, huh?
Niide, let's drink till we drop!
Got it.
-Cheers. -Cheers. Thanks.
-You drank waaay too much. -I'm not drunk.
Stairs ahead. Turning here.
-We're boarding. -Wait a sec...
-Whoa, whoa. -We're boarding.
Oh, sorry.
Excuse me...
Do you know the trolley problem?
Huh?
The trolley problem.
The one about the uncontrollable trolley on the rails?
Yes.
If the trolley runs straight,
five workers on the track ahead die.
If you press a button to divert it to save those five,
one different worker on the other track dies.
Now, if you were there, would you press that button?
I think... I'd try to save the five some other way.
Interesting...
Then let's change the rules a bit.
Say there's one person straight ahead,
and five on the other line.
And all you can do is press the button, or not.
And what if the solo person is...
your wife.
Would you kill the five?
I guess it's hard to answer a question like that out of the blue.
Yeah.
But there'll come a day when you have to decide.
See you around, Detective.
"Detective?" Hey, wait...
The person I admire the most is my dad.
He is a doctor.
My dad's job is saving people's lives.
I want to become someone who can save people, just like him.
I'm home.
You weren't always this studious. Did you decide on a goal?
Yeah, police officer.
Huh, I wouldn't have guessed.
Did you decide to do what's right for society?
I think Mom had an unhappy life.
I'm not so sure. She had you, after all.
It was because of me that she couldn't leave that jerk.
I couldn't protect her.
This is Carrot-Man. He's kind of a... good-luck charm.
Feel free to throw him out.
Why a carrot?
Your short fuse is because you don't eat enough carrots.
Irrelevant.
Promise Carrot-Man that you won't get angry.
No.
So you don’t want him?
No... I'll keep him.
Thanks.
Ah, they're starting. Let's go.
What?
-So pretty. -Awesome.
Let's do this again.
-Next year? -Yes, next year.
And the year after.
Yeah. Every year, together.
We'll watch them together every year.
12 HOURS UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
TOKYO FESTIVAL 2026
Welcome to TOKYO FESTIVAL. Parade starts at 10 AM. Fireworks at 7 PM.
What a turnout.
Lot of tourists, too.
And VIPs from all over the world.
VIPs?
Mic test, mic test. One, two, three.
-How is it? -Okay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Akina? Sorry, I'll call back if you're busy.
It's fine. What's up?
It's just about Toshiro.
What did he do this time?
No, he's been transferred to the Homicide Division.
Huh? So his dream has come true at last. That's fantastic.
Thanks.
But he's gonna get even busier, isn't he?
You haven't told him about the test yet, right?
Well... no.
How's holding back gonna help? Think about yourself for a change.
Sorry, there's a patient. I'll call you back.
Is everything okay?
Huh?
-He's all yours. -Okay.
Take care.
Take your time.
-Hey there. -Hello.
Have you had lunch? I've got one left.
-Can I buy that? -Sure can!
I'll knock 200 yen off.
You're too kind.
I LOVE YOU MOMMY
Is that by your... daughter?
Yup. My pride and joy. Cute as a button, unlike me.
She's my reason for living. My whole life, even.
I'm jealous.
Of course, it's not all easy.
That van was also there yesterday. I wonder what it is.
A florist, perhaps?
Maybe a coincidence.
FLOWER SHOP ATRA
What's the occasion?
I want to give my daughter a bouquet.
Come on in.
How about something like this?
Wow, they're distinctive. Would a kid like these?
They have a unique fragrance. I'm sure your daughter will appreciate them.
Oh, yes.
How do you know she's blind?
That's a message from us.
THE GAME BEGINS IN 5 HOURS.
What's...
Welcome. Can I help you?
The other shop assistant...
I'm the only one working here.
Niide.
-A VIP will pass Point A shortly. -Okay.
-Be on alert. -Yes, sir.
Hi, guys.
Good to see you.
They got you on security?
You Community Safety guys don't have it easy.
Niide got transferred to the Homicide Division.
So I heard.
Congrats. Saori was delighted.
It's your wedding anniversary, too.
Just go back to your post.
And? What did you get for her?
-Huh? -Huh?
You didn't get her anything?
Don't you know you only made it this far thanks to her?
Of course, I'm grateful.
You know what's troubling her?
Kinda...
I think you need to address that.
Yeah.
Excuse me. Do you have Hoshikuzu beer?
I'm sorry, we don't stock that.
I see. Thank you.
We're done, but keep an eye out. I'll notify you on pullout.
Yes, sir.
-Niide. -Yes.
Could you see the guests to their car?
But I'm off-duty now, sir.
Come on... take one for your old team.
All right, sir.
MUSIC ACHIEVEMENT SHOWCASE
DONGHAE ARTS CENTER
-This way. -Thank you.
Rian, your dad's here.
Rian.
Dad!
You look lovely.
This is for you.
Thanks. They smell nice.
Mom... really wanted to come, but she had too much work.
That's a shame, huh
It's okay. You made it.
You know, I can see it.
No matter where, no matter when, I can see your smile, Dad.
Thank you.
1 HOUR UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
Niide.
I'll write the report. Please, go home.
I owe you one. Thanks.
Welcome.
The language... of flowers...
"Together forever."
"You are perfect."
"Dearest."
This is it.
Can I get eleven white roses?
Found it.
Well, you had everyone transfixed today.
You were like an angel.
-Really? -Yup.
I wish Mom could have seen.
I'll be sure to bring Mom next time, okay?
Okay.
Just a sec.
EMERGENCY. CALL BACK AT ONCE.
Uh, Rian, just a sec.
Up we go.
I just have to make a quick call to the hospital.
-Can you wait for me here? -Okay.
This is Han Kiju. I got a message about an emergency.
Ah, Dr. Han. I'll check right away.
Please do.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, it's fine.
SORRY, RUNNING A BIT LATE
1 MINUTE UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
I'm telling you, I got a message about an emergency.
But nobody here says they sent the message.
What on earth...?
What pretty flowers.
Thank you.
Doesn't this smell nice too?
30 SECONDS UNTIL THE START OF KIDNAP GAME
What color do you think this rose is?
Red?
No.
It's black.
It's a black rose.
SORRY, RUNNING A BIT LATE
And now it's time for the main event.
In a few moments,
the fireworks bearing our hopes and dreams will light up the sky.
Now let's bring the Tokyo night sky to life with the ultimate countdown!
Here we go!
Ten! Nine! Eight! Seven! Six!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Rian?
Rian!
Saori?
Something happen?
-She saw a kidnapping. -Tell us what you remember.
-I saw... -Mrs. Tadokoro.
Your wife!
I saw a florist take your wife away!
-Huh? -I really saw it!
Pause it.
That's Saori.
Please play it.
That's Saori. My wife.
Code red! Track down the van.
Yes, sir.
-You said it was a florist. -My wife did.
Yes! This is the van.
It turned right at the tee.
Rian can't see. She wouldn't go home on her own!
Please calm down.
How do you expect me to calm down?!
It was a woman.
She left these rose petals behind.
Have any of you seen my daughter?
Have none of you seen her?
My daughter is about... about this tall...
She's wearing a white coat.
If anyone has seen her, please tell me!
Stand back, stand back. Please make way.
-Make way. -Coming through.
-Here's a copy of the map. -Thanks.
They can't be far. Hyodo, where's the van?
Um, I don't...
-Use the N System, goddammit! -Calm down!
Don't forget, you're a part to this, so...
I know that!
She's my wife!
That's why I...
Hold on.
You know it's standard procedure to wait for the demands in a missing persons case.
The SIT is taking over. There are press controls in place.
Your job is to cooperate.
AKINA ISOBE
Hello?
I heard about Saori.
I can't talk.
Listen! Watch the video I'm sending you.
Breaking news.
There is still an uproar outside this concert hall in Seoul.
An 11-year-old girl who performed just hours before
has been kidnapped by an unknown party.
South Korea?
The despicable crime was swiftly committed amid a crowd.
-What's this? -A girl was kidnapped in Seoul.
-At the same time as Saori. -So what?
People in other Asian cities were kidnapped at the same time as Saori, too.
Even the same rose petals.
In Singapore, a man was abducted in a restaurant.
-Ms. Janice? -Yeah. I've got this text from Tony.
"Sorry, I’ll be a bit late...." "No hurry, take your time"
-Is this the last time you communicate with him? -Yes.
In Bangkok, a woman was taken from her home.
You can't enter.
I live here.
Go on.
Dao!! Come back!!
In Manila, a young woman was abducted on her way home.
Maria?!
-Maria! -Sir! Do not enter, sir!
Let me go! Maria’s my granddaughter!
Please! Get back, sir. Please!
In Taipei, a man was abducted in front of his daughter.
Leona!
Rui, come on.
Mind your step.
Leona.
Dad...
No photos!
This isn't out yet, but there was a kidnapping in Naha, too.
The perp may contact you. Wait here.
Yes.
Kidnappings occurred in seven Asian cities simultaneously.
What's happening?
I'll call when I know more.
KIDNAPPINGS IN SEVEN ASIAN CITIES
The world's in uproar about it!
What on earth is going on?
I'll check for updates.
SAORI KIDNAP GAME
"kiDnap GAME"?
"You have been enlisted in the kiDnap GAME."
"Rules.
"Each player has been given a mission."
"Complete your mission before the others
"if you want to save your loved one."
"The time limit is ten days.
"The game will end if a player completes the assigned mission."
"Players deemed incapable of completing their mission will be
"immediately disqualified."
"Do not notify or request assistance from state authorities.
"Rule-breakers will be disqualified.
"Only one shall prevail... Only one shall survive..."
Only one shall prevail...
MISSION
KIDNAP GAME CO-PRODUCTION PARTNERSHIP
FUJI TELEVISION MAKERVILLE SIMSTORY
BASED ON KIDNAP GAME CREATED BY YUSUKE KATO
MkvDrama.net